<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<armor> 
  <type id="1"> 
    <name>Snake Armor</name>  
    <image>image/SnakeHarness.jpg</image>  
    <description>Snake Armor is a gear set Dungeons and Dragons. It’s a medium set which has a great armor rating and provides near immunity to poison.To obtain it, you’ll have to find the diagrams for it, a bunch of materials and a capable artisan. You’ll need to craft the gear. Wire x4Hardened Leather x4 Leather Straps x5 Linen x4 Cured Draconid Leather x1</description> 
  </type>  
  <type id="2"> 
    <name>Kendo Armor</name>  
    <image>image/KendoArmor.jpg</image>  
    <description>Kendo Armor is a heavy armor set in Dungeons and Dragons. It boasts some of the highest elemental resistances and physical defense in the game. Physical Defence : 30, Defence : 22, Weight : 7.5lbs, Value : 300</description> 
  </type>  
  <type id="3"> 
    <name>Leather Jacket</name>  
    <image>image/LeatherJacket.jpg</image>  
    <description>The armor is mostly made of leather and is lightweight, making it ideal for the agile shadow-hugging thief. It offers higher defense than Elven or Scaled Armor and is available extremely early in the game after 2 non combat quests. Incidentally, the armor cannot be disenchanted. Upgraded with Leather. The Armor upgrade has carrying capacity +35 instead of +20. Base Armor : 68, Weight : 11lbs, Base Value : 1679</description> 
  </type>  
  <type id="4"> 
    <name>Sentinel Coat</name>  
    <image>image/SentinelCoat.jpg</image>  
    <description>The Sentinel armor is a vacuum-sealed asbestos jumpsuit covering the entire body. Attached to it is the interface and mounts for the T-45d power armor. Its purpose is twofold - it allows the user to actually operate the armor and protect soft tissue from heat and moving parts inside the suit. It is a decent option for stealth and sniper mercantile-based characters who seek an alternative to combat armor or Talon combat armor. Its good Damage Resistance and its Sneak bonus make it a good choice for early-game characters. Weight : 20lbs, Value : 1000</description> 
  </type>  
  <type id="5"> 
    <name>Red Lotus</name>  
    <image>image/RedLotus.jpg</image>  
    <description>The Superior Death Lotus chestplate is ranged body armour. Wearing a Red Lotus armour set (including augmented parts, but not weapons) grants a passive ability, Death Knot, which gives a chance to obtain a ports resource crate when defeating an opponent. Value : 1200, Weight : 8lbs</description> 
  </type>  
</armor>
