<weapon>
	<type id="1">
		<name>Steel Sword</name>
		<image>image/SteelSword.jpg</image>
		<description>The Steel Sword is a one-handed weapon.
The sword has a steel blade as to be expected, with some rugged designs
on the bottom edges.
The hilt appears to be made of a fine wood, with metal woven into it,
while the base of the blade has complex line patterns, with some dark
gray areas.
It can be forged at a blacksmith's forge with the following components:
1 x Leather Strip
2 x Steel Ingot
1 x Iron Ingot
Base Damage : 8, Weight : 10, Baase Value : 45</description>
	</type>
	<type id="2">
		<name>Crossbow</name>
		<image>image/Crossbow.jpg</image>
		<description>Crossbows are projectile weapons in Dungeons and Dragons.
Crossbows differ from bows in a number of ways. They use different
ammunition, projectiles are loaded instead of nocked, and they
provide a number of advantages and disadvantages compared to the
standard bow.
Two types of crossbow bolts are available — steel bolts and dwarven
bolts.
Crossbows have a built-in 50% chance to stagger opponents.
		</description>
	</type>
	<type id="3">
		<name>Thane Steel Battle Axe</name>
		<image>image/ThaneSteelBattleAxe.jpg</image>
		<description>Axe of Whiterun is one of a unique group of weapons found
in Dungeons and Dragons.
an identical version can be crafted with the generic material and a
matching enchantment applied. The weapon may also be titled with the
same name during enchanting.
The upgrade material is dependent on the material that the weapon was
generated with.
This item also benefits from whichever Smithing perk is related to the
material of the axe.
		</description>
	</type>
	<type id="4">
		<name>Dwarven Bow Skinned</name>
		<image>image/DwarvenBowSkinned.jpg</image>
		<description>Dwrven Bow is very powerful with a decent base damage and
nice fire rate

Base damage: 13
Shots per second: 0.75
Skin: Dwarven Bow coloured black</description>
	</type>
	<type id="5">
		<name>Dragon Battle Axe</name>
		<image>image/DragonBattleAxe.jpg</image>
		<description>The Dragonbone Battleaxe is a two-handed weapon.
It can be forged at a blacksmith's forge with the following components:
3 x Dragon Bones
2 x Ebony Ingots
2 x Leather Strips
Base Damage : 26, Weight : 30, Base Value : 3000</description>
	</type>
</weapon>
