<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<helmet>
	<type id="1">
		<name>Light Helm</name>
		<image>image/LightHelm.jpg</image>
		<description>
			This gold and mithral helm looks like the bristle-bearded head of a
			manticore.
			A helm of the hunter grants you a +5 com­petence bonus on Spot checks
			and the benefit of the Far Shot feat. These effects function
			continuously.
			When you activate this helm, you gain low-light vision and darkvision out
			to 60 feet for 4 hours. This ability functions once per day.
			<p> Cost to Create: 4500, 360 XP, 9 days.</p>
		</description>
	</type>
	<type id="2">
		<name>Crested Helmet</name>
		<image>image/CrestHelmet.jpg</image>
		<description>
			A crested helmet or cassis crista, is a heavy, all-enclosing helmet
			with grill-like visor. This helmet is usually made of bronze and
			decorated with a plume crest.
			The great helm only grants its AC bonus if you are wearing light or no
			armor (it is assumed that a suit medium and heavy armor already
			provides head protection). In addition, you have disadvantage on
			Wisdom (Perception) checks while wearing a great helm.
			<p>Cost : 15gp , Armor Class : +1, Strength : 13, Weight : 5lb</p>
		</description>
	</type>
	<type id="3">
		<name>Imperial Close Helm</name>
		<image>image/ImperialHelmetClosed.jpg</image>
		<description>The Imperial Helmet is a piece of heavy armor and part of
			the Imperial Armor set. It is a full-face variant of the Imperial
			Officer's Helmet, but is relatively rare and can only be found in
			three locations.
			Base Armor : 18, Weight : 5lb, Base Value : 30
		</description>
	</type>
	<type id="4">
		<name>Steel Horned Helmet</name>
		<image>image/SteelHornedHelmet.jpg</image>
		<description>The Steel Horned Helmet is a piece of heavy armor and
			part of the steel armor set found in The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim.
			Steel Armor requires a Smithing level of 20 and the Steel Smithing
			perk to create. It can be forged at a blacksmith's forge with the
			following components:
			2 × Leather Strips
			2 × Steel Ingots
			1 × Iron Ingot
			It can be upgraded with a steel ingot at a workbench and also benefits
			from the Steel Smithing perk, which doubles the improvement.
		</description>
	</type>
	<type id="5">
		<name>Dukaan Mask</name>
		<image>image/DukaanMask.jpg</image>
		<description>Dukaan (Dovahzul: , "Dishonor") is a dragon priest mask
			found in Dungeons and Dragons.
			It can be upgraded with an ebony ingot at a workbench, and also
			benefits from the Daedric Smithing perk, which doubles the
			improvement.
			Base Armor : 23, Weight : 9, Base Value : 500</description>
	</type>
</helmet>
